(Music by Anna Oxygen)
(موسيقى أننا أوكسيچين)
(Music: "Shells" by Mirah)
(المقطوعة الموسيقية: "شيلز" لـ ميرا)
♪ You learned how to be a diver ♪
♪ تعلمت كيف تكون غواص ♪
♪ Put on a mask and believe ♪
♪ فلتضع قناعا وتؤمن ♪
♪ Gather a dinner of shells for me ♪
♪ ولتجمع المحار عشاءا لي ♪
♪ Take the tank down so you can breathe ♪
♪ خذ اسطوانة معك لتستطيع التنفس ♪
♪ Below ♪
♪ وأنت بأسفل ♪
♪ Movements slow ♪
♪ الحركات تأتي برفق ♪
♪ You are an island ♪
♪ أنت جزيرة ♪
♪ All the secrets until then ♪
♪ وكل الأسرار حتى ذلك الحين ♪
♪ Pried open I held them ♪
♪ نُزعت وأنا استمسكت بها ♪
♪ Until they were still ♪
♪ حتى آصبحت ساكنه ♪
(Music)
(موسيقى)
(Music by Caroline Lufkin)
(موسيقى لـ كارولين لوفكين)
(Music by Anna Oxygen)
(موسيقى لـ أننا أوكسيچين)
♪ Dream time, I will find you ♪
♪ ساعة الحلم, سأجدك ♪
♪ You are shady, you are new ♪
♪ تحيطك الظلال, أنت جديد ♪
♪ I'm not so good at mornings ♪
♪ لا أكون جيدة أبدا في صبوح الأيام ♪
♪ I can see too clearly ♪
♪ أستطيع أنا أرى بوضوح فائق ♪
♪ I prefer the nighttime ♪
♪ أفضل أوقات الليل ♪
♪ Dark and blurry ♪
♪ بظلمتها وضبابيتها ♪
♪ Falling night ♪
♪ الليل الساقط ♪
♪ Hovering light ♪
♪ الضوء المحلق ♪
♪ Calling night ♪
♪ الليل المنادي ♪
♪ In the moontime I will give up my life ♪
♪ في الليالي القمرية سوف أتخلى عن حياتي ♪
♪ And in the deep dreams ♪
♪ وفي الأحلام العميقة ♪
♪ You will find me ♪
♪ ستجدني ♪
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
[Excerpts from "Myth and Infrastructure"]
[أقتباسات من "الأسطورة والبنية التحتية"]
Bruno Giussani: Come back.
برونو جيزاني: فلتعودوا مجددا.
Miwa Matreyek!
ميوا ماترايك!
(Applause)
(تصقيق)